{
    "id": "016e63668c204cc3a7d9567baa886e3b",
    "title": "Underline the prepositions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "64666a9c432e4557999a4398b9f19b5e",
            "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Humpty Dumpty sat ........................ a wall.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The lion and the unicorn fought ........................... the crown.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "for",
                        "about"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Little Jack Horner sat ...................... a corner.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Wee Willie Winkie runs ....................... the town.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "across",
                        "over",
                        "through"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "A fair little girl sat ....................... a tree.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "below",
                        "under",
                        "down"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I bring fresh showers for the thirsty flowers .......................... the seas and the streams.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "from",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She laid her arms .......................... her breast.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "across",
                        "above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I tried to reason him ............................. his fears.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "out of",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He swore ...................... the nine Gods.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "by",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "One day the boy took his breakfast and ate it by a purling brook which ran ......................... his motherâ€™s orchard.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "through",
                        "about"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "One crowded hour of glorious life is worth an age ....................... a name.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "without",
                        "against",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}